(This drama is related to specific characters, institutions, and groups It has nothing to do with the case and is purely fictitious (I hereby inform you)
(本剧与特定人物 机构 团体 案件无关 纯属虚构 特此告知)
Dingchen
定辰
scared me
吓我一跳
I made a little preparation
我小小准备了一番
A little care
一点小心意
Why do you bother so much?
你何必那么费心
where are people
人在哪里
there
那里
I'm curious about something now
我现在有件事很好奇
What did you say?
什么事 你说
(Episode 15) When I was in Lishui
(第15集) 当初在丽水时
why did you choose me
你为什么选择了我
Tetsuo has a good family background and is good at studying.
哲雄家世背景好 又会念书
Why do you like me like this poor rural high school student
你为什么看上像我这样 贫穷的农高生
Really, are you still curious?
真是的 你到现在还很好奇吗
Yes
对
so if you were me I would choose Tetsuo-ra
所以如果你是我 就会选择哲雄罗
That's of course
那是当然的
After all, Li Douxue’s future is gloomy.
毕竟李斗学的前途一片灰暗
This is the difference between us
这就是我们之间的不同
We look at people differently
我们看人的眼光不同
What's the difference
哪里不同
I'm also good at reading people.
我也很会看人
Tetsuo's family is indeed very rich
哲雄他们家的确很有钱
Or a family of independence activists?
还是独立运动家的家族
Wealth and fame are both dazzling
财富和名誉兼备 耀眼不已
Tetsuo is just Just on that dazzling ship
哲雄不过是 在那艘耀眼的船上罢了
Put it this way I'm on a boat in the dark
这么说来 我就是在黑暗中的船上罗
That's not the case
才不是那样呢
Although your family is very poor
虽然你们家很贫穷
But your eyes are always like the stars in the morning sparkling
但你的双眼总像清晨的星星般 闪闪发光
The darker the place, the brighter it shines
在越黑暗的地方越是闪耀
Most people grow up in this environment Everybody will lose hope
一般人在这种环境下长大 都会失去希望
Do I have that?
我有那样吗
Yes
有
But there is a more important reason
不过 有个更重要的原因
(Note: The youngest daughter of the King of Goguryeo Plains) Because I want to be Princess Ping Gang
(注:高句丽平原王小女儿) 因为我想成为平冈公主
Princess Ping Gang?
平冈公主吗
(Note: Husband of Princess Pinggang) So am I a fool, Wenda?
(注:平冈公主之夫) 所以我是傻瓜温达吗
That's right
没错
I'm probably a born filmmaker.
我应该是个天生的电影制片人吧
I want to turn a fool into the strongest general
我要把傻瓜变成最强的将军
Show dramatic plot twists
展现出戏剧化的情节转折
Don't you think it's great?
不觉得很赞吗
so what you mean is
所以你的意思是
in the movie of your life
在你的人生电影中
I am the actor chosen by you
我是被你选上的演员
That's right
没错
Sounds really sad
听起来真让人伤心
Douxue, these are not important
斗学 这些都不重要
You grew up in such a difficult environment But he can still be a kind person
你在这么艰难的环境下长大 却还能成为一个善良的人
makes me feel grateful
让我觉得心怀感激
When you feel torment because of Tetsuo
你因为哲雄而感到煎熬时
I also felt sympathy for you
我也曾对你感到同情
The clear eyes you look at me with
你看着我的那双清澈双眼
Always so sincere and touching
总是那么真诚 令人动容
Probably all of this combined
大概是这所有一切加起来
Only then can I fall in love with you
才会让我爱上你吧
This is the case until now
直到现在也是如此
Dingchen
定辰
What's wrong
怎么了
Are you touched?
你很感动吗
"I know very well that we love each other"
"我很清楚 我们彼此相爱着"
"We all know it"
"我们都很清楚"
"We will keep each other in our hearts Love so deeply"
"我们将彼此刻在心上 那样地深爱着"
Be my princess Ping Gang
做我的平冈公主吧
I will repay what I owe you throughout my life
欠你的 我会用一辈子来偿还
"The aroma burned by the hot sun"
"被烈日烧灼的香气"
Li Douxue, what are you doing?
李斗学 你是怎样
i'm very disappointed in you
我对你很失望
Diamonds are so small
钻石这么小颗
Really?
是吗
I thought you liked plain styles
我以为你喜欢朴素的款式
That’s why I found small diamonds
所以才找了小颗的钻石
Got it. I'll buy something as big as this.
知道了 我去买这么大颗的过来
Put it on for me
帮我戴上吧
Put it on for me, silly Wenda
快帮我戴上 傻瓜温达
"I want to find you but I can't leave"
"想去找你却无法动身"
"I want to see you but I can't see you"
"想要见你却见不到你"
"can only remain in eternity"
"只能留存在永恒之中"
"I want to find you but I can't leave"
"想去找你却无法动身"
"I want to see you but I can't see you"
"想要见你却见不到你"
"can only remain in eternity"
"只能留存在永恒之中"
Douxue thank you
斗学 谢谢你
And I don't need any diamonds
还有 我不需要什么钻石
you are my diamond
你就是我的钻石
If you take my diamond away He's dead
你要是把我的钻石抢走 就死定了
So we should never be separated for the rest of our lives
所以我们一辈子都别分开
Dingchen thank you
定辰 谢谢你
i love you too
我也爱你
"Even the moments that must be forgotten"
"连必须忘却的瞬间"
"I still love you"
"我都还爱着你"
Li Douxue’s whereabouts are unknown Registered as deceased
李斗学下落不明 被登记为死亡人口
No one has entered the country using the name Li Douxue.
也没有人用李斗学这个名字入境
The results of photo surveillance are displayed
照片监识的结果显示
That man The name of Lee Hyung-guk, an overseas Chinese in Japan
那个男人以 在日侨胞李亨国的名字
Departing from Tokyo and arriving at Gimpo Airport
从东京出发 由金浦机场入境
(Special Assistant Cui Zhexiong) Monitor all his actions
(特别辅佐官 崔哲雄) 监视他所有的行动
Report to me one-five-ten. Do you understand?
一五一十向我报告 知道了吗
Why are you still standing there?
还愣在那里干嘛
OK get out
好的 给我出去
Puff puff Why are you still preparing this?
噗噗 你们怎么还准备这个
The cake is so beautiful welcome
蛋糕还真漂亮 欢迎光临
Congratulations on boarding our ship
恭喜你坐上了我们这艘船
Congratulations
恭喜您
hope to be safe Overcome the wind and waves and land smoothly
希望能够平安地 越过风浪 顺利上岸
Definitely will
一定会的
Of course
那是当然
After all, our captain is great
毕竟我们的船长很了不起
He came from the sea of death Where are the people who came back alive?
他可是从死亡的大海上 活着回来的人呢
Come, our eldest brother and sister-in-law
来 我们的大哥和大嫂
Please make a wish to never be separated from each other again
请许下和彼此再也不分离的愿望
Come on, blow out the candles and eat the cake.
快点吹蜡烛吃蛋糕吧
OK
好的
Dingchen, come on
定辰 来吧
one two
一 二
Come and pay homage to our bride-to-be.
来 敬我们的准新娘定辰
Cheers
干杯
(Restaurant rice soup)
(饭店汤饭)
wait for me
等我一下
Hello, this is the hotel soup rice
您好 这里是饭店汤饭
Someone is following you
有人在跟踪你们
Who sent it?
是谁派来的
Cui Zhexiong
崔哲雄
I provided an important piece of information
我提供了一个重要的情报
Li Douxue must also give me equivalent information.
李斗学也必须给我对等的情报
Who wants to kill me?
究竟是谁要杀我
Ask him to come with evidence
叫他带着证据过来
Dingchen seems to have become more beautiful
定辰好像变得更漂亮了
She was very beautiful...
她本来就很漂亮…
Someone is following us
有人在跟踪我们
what
什么
It seems your identity has been exposed
你的身分好像曝光了
That guy Wu Wanxu...
吴万旭那个家伙…
not him
不是他
It’s Choi Cheol-woong
是崔哲雄
what did you say
你说什么
Leave quietly through the back door of the kitchen
低调地从厨房后门离开吧
This place will be temporarily closed for a while.
这边要暂时停业一阵子了
Brother, our plan needs to be stepped up.
哥 我们的计划要加紧脚步了
Got it
知道了
Douxue, let’s go see Tetsuo
斗学 去见哲雄吧
don't escape
不要逃避
I'll go with you too
我也跟你一起去
He can't do anything to you anyway
反正他也不能对你怎么样
I'll meet him
我会见他的
After all, you have to give him a chance
毕竟总要给他一次机会
Although he may have changed
虽然他也可能已经变了
But I can go alone
不过我一个人去就好
I'll go too
我也一起去
It's not convenient for us to talk if you come.
你来的话 我们不方便谈
And you know it too
而且你也知道啊
There are some issues that need to be discussed separately between the two of us.
有些问题需要我们两个单独说开
Since Tetsuo has already called General
既然哲雄都喊出将军了
We must also respond
我们也必须有所回应才行
That guy was the one who was entrusted
受到委托的是那个家伙
As for the client…
至于委托人…
he's coming
他来了
Li Douxue is back alive
李斗学活着回来了
i know
我知道
How could you...
你怎么会…
Then you know his cash cow? Where did it come from?
那你知道他生财的摇钱树 是哪来的吗
Money tree?
摇钱树吗
If I tell everything truthfully
如果我全都如实禀告
Please put that guy Li Douxue in jail
请你把李斗学那小子关进监狱
and guarantee that I can continue to maintain businessman status
并保证我能继续维持 事业家的身分
You guy...
你这家伙…
You say it
你说吧
Li Douxue is with me Operating an illegal underground casino
李斗学跟我一起 经营非法地下赌场
What to run
经营什么
Illegal underground casino?
非法地下赌场吗
Yes
对
He and I jointly hold shares
他跟我共同持有股分
There are currently about 15 casinos across the country
目前全国上下约有15间赌场
Where and what did Li Douxue do in the future?
往后李斗学在哪里做了什么事
Let me be your prosecutor's spy
就让我当检察官您的眼线
You can contact me anytime
您可以随时跟我联络
Can you believe it now?
你现在能相信了吧
Even if I don't kill you, you will still die.
就算我不杀你 你也是死路一条
If that kid drags his feet
要是那个小子拖拖拉拉地
Cui Zhexiong may entrust others to do it
崔哲雄有可能会委托别人动手
If you are afraid Just hide away from the limelight
你要是怕的话 就赶快躲去避风头
But then I will lose everything
但那样我就会失去一切
money you earned in the past It should allow you to have enough food and clothing for the rest of your life, right?
你过去赚到的钱 应该能让你余生不愁吃穿了吧
Compared to the money I earned helping that family That little money is nothing at all
比起我帮那家人赚来的钱 那点钱根本不算什么
Besides, even my money
况且连我那些钱
They all have ways to take it all for themselves
他们都有办法全占为己有
I have to take the initiative first and then retreat unscathed.
我要先主动出击再全身而退才行
Reveal Huang Zhongcheng’s secret funds
抖出黄忠诚的秘密资金
That's impossible
那是不可能的事
Change the target to Jiang Ruzhen’s money...
把目标换成姜汝珍的钱…
There's a chance
就有机会了
(Apgujeong Accounting Firm)
(狎鸥亭会计事务所)
(Liang Xingjin)
(梁星谨)
You…
你…
May I ask who you are?
请问你是哪位
Hello, thank you for your hard work
您好 辛苦您了
Please drink this drink
这饮料请您喝
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦您了
Miss Song Yanzhu
宋妍珠小姐
you are so beautiful
你真漂亮
Alas
唉唷
how are you doing
您过得好吗
Of course I've always had a good time
当然 我一直都过得不错
if you don't mind
您不介意的话
Can I trouble you to sign your name for me?
我能麻烦您帮我签个名吗
Let's get the business done first.
我们先把正事谈完吧
ok of course
好的 这是当然的
Please sit down
请坐
This is the building owner of Apgujeong
这位是狎鸥亭的大楼主人
This guy needs no introduction. You know it very well, right?
这位不用多作介绍 您也很清楚吧
hello
你好
nice to meet you
很开心见到你
The building manager has already taken me to visit
大楼管理员已经带我去参观过了
No water leakage problem
没有漏水问题
In very good condition
状态很不错
Of course That's a new building that was built just a few years ago.
当然罗 那可是才盖好几年的新大楼
Of course the condition is good
状态当然好
Because of personal reasons, our wife
我们夫人因为私人因素
Will be sold at an unprecedented price
才会以破天荒的价格出售
How about it? Have you decided?
怎么样 您决定好了吗
Please help me negotiate the price
请帮我砍价吧
what
什么
This building is too big
这栋大楼实在太大了
It's not easy for me to raise funds
我要筹措资金不太容易
Help me cut... 500 million won
帮我砍个…五亿韩元吧
This makes me a little embarrassed
这样我有点为难呢
I've sold it very cheaply
我已经卖得很便宜了
I insist on a signing bonus of 10 billion won
我坚持签约金100亿韩元
The final payment is 2 billion won
尾款20亿韩元
Otherwise I won’t sell it
不然我就不卖
Our wife really did it because of personal reasons
我们夫人真的是因为私人因素
Why would they sell it urgently at such an unprecedented price?
才会以这么破天荒的价格急售
Otherwise…
不然…
Help me cut 300 million won
帮我砍个3亿韩元吧
This gives me a headache
这样我很头痛呢
Madam, what do you think?
夫人 您意下如何呢
Don’t you also know about my son?
你不也知道我儿子的事吗
Otherwise, both of you should think about it for another day.
不然两位都各再考虑一天吧
If there are other buyers who want to buy during the period
要是期间有其他买家想要购入
There's nothing we can do about it
那也没办法
Just do it
就这么做吧
Sorry I just asked for your signature...
不好意思 我刚刚拜托您的签名…
Just wait until the contract is signed and I will sign it for you together.
就等签约时 我再一起签给您吧
OK
好的
How embarrassing
真让人尴尬呢
Let's wait a little longer
我们再等一等吧
Accountant Liang
梁会计师
Do you want to have a cup of tea with me
您要和我喝杯茶吗
Okay, thank you for your hard work
好的 辛苦您了
Let's finish well
好好收尾吧
Thanks
谢了
We haven't seen each other for so long
我们那么久没见了
You came to me for this kind of thing
你竟然是为了这种事来拜托我
sorry
抱歉
If you feel sorry, don't ask me
觉得抱歉就不要拜托我
You asked me to break up with you because you were in jail.
你因为入狱 就拜托我和你分手
Now, please ask me to act this kind of fraud
现在则来拜托我演这种诈骗戏码
This matter will not involve you
这件事不会牵连到你的
I also want to ask you something
我也拜托你一件事
With you at the speed of a super express train Married and divorced
和你用超特快列车的速度 结婚又离婚
Although it was because of this that I was able to quickly return to the film industry
虽然因此我才能迅速回归影坛
But I forgot your speed
但我忘记你的速度
as slow as a tram
就像电车那样缓慢
Come back to me again
重新回到我身边吧
Are you planning to retire again?
你又打算息影吗
I might go to jail again
我说不定又要去坐牢
You still show loyalty It’s more important than love
你仍旧把义气 看得比爱情还重要啊
No, my fate is terrible
不是 我的命格很烂
You will only become unhappy if you are with me
你跟我在一起只会变得不幸
sorry thank you
对不起 谢谢你
I won't contact you again
我不会再跟你联络了
You have to live a good life
你要好好过日子
good
好
I won't wait for you anymore
我也不会再等你了
"What kind of person should I prepare to meet?"
"我该准备遇见怎样的人呢"
"But please remember"
"但是请你记得"
"I didn't understand until after we broke up"
"在分手之后我才明白"
"You are my love"
"你是我的爱"
(Camellia Nursery)
(山茶花育幼院)
where
在哪里
she is inside
她在里面
Are you sure?
确定吗
Yes we are sure
对 我们很确定
Douxue, Zhenyu will be frightened
斗学 贞玉会被吓到的
I'll go find her first
我先去找她
good
好
Zhenyu
贞玉
Sister Dingchen
定辰姊
how do you know i'm here
你怎么知道我在这里
Your brother is here too
你哥也一起来了
Brother Douxue?
斗学哥吗
You are still the same now Will you run away from home when I'm not around?
你现在还是一样 我不在你就离家出走吗
Brother Dou Xue
斗学哥
what's going on
这是怎么回事
To take you home
我为了带你回家
Came back from the underworld
从阴间回来了
(Boss Xu Guili)
(许贵礼老板)
Mom, I'm sorry
妈 对不起
It’s okay…
没事…
my baby thank you
我的宝贝 谢谢你
thank you
谢谢你
Very good. Just come back.
很好 回来就好
Don't come here again
你之后别再来了
And don't send any more pocket money.
也别再寄零用钱来了
Brother Dongxiu
东秀哥
I will be pardoned and released soon
我很快就会被特赦释放
Really?
真的吗
Great. I will tell my comrades
太好了 我会去跟同志们说
Don't
不要
Don't tell them
你不要跟他们说
what
什么
After going out...
出去之后…
I might not be able to see you again
我可能就不能再跟你见面了
what does this mean
这是什么意思
You can scold me if you want
你要骂我也行
I will take a different path from you in the future
以后我会走上跟你们不同的道路
Thank you very much these days
这些日子很谢谢你
Why did you suddenly say that?
你怎么突然这么说
Brother Dongxiu…
东秀哥…
Is it possible to make that much money?
有可能赚那么多钱吗
Too outrageous
太离谱了
(Seoul City Government Estimated Income Report Ministry of Construction)
(首尔市政府预估收益报告书 建设部)
This is when Shuixi Residential Area opens for special subscription Estimated revenue from the Ministry of Construction and the Seoul Metropolitan Government
这是水西住宅区开放特别认购时 建设部和首尔市政府预估的收益
President, the amount you told your wife There is a big difference between this and this.
会长您向夫人说的金额 跟这个有很大的出入呢
That's because civil servants don't know very well
那是因为公务员不太清楚
Costs not listed on the estimate There are so many
估价单上面没有列出的花费 可多得很呢
Team leader, you know it very well, right?
组长您也很清楚吧
Anyway, Madam, she is very disappointed now
总之夫人她现在很失望
So Madam, do you want to get more money?
所以夫人想要拿到更多钱吗
This is absolutely impossible
这是绝对不可能的事
Then take away the madam's money.
那就把夫人的钱抽掉吧
what
什么
How can we now talk about withdrawing funds...
现在说要把资金抽掉怎么可以…
If the minister finds out about this matter
这件事要是被部长知道了
Madam will be in trouble
夫人会很为难的
These are the capitation accounts for our organization
这些是我们单位的人头帐户
Just divide the money into ten equal parts and remit it.
把钱分成十等份汇进来就可以了
We decided to increase your profit share
我们决定增加您的分润
But there is no way to increase it too much
但没办法增加太多
You also know about this case
您也知道 这次的案子
There are many expenses that are not recorded on the financial statements
有许多没记在财务报表上的开支
Yes
是啊
This also includes when the investment case fails.
其中也包含了投资案失败时
You have to make some profits, right?
也得赚取的利润吧
Will you propose a partnership investment to me? The biggest purpose is also for this
您会对我提议合伙投资案 最大的目的也是为了这个
I will give you another 5% profit share
我会再给您5%的分润
no more
不能再多了
Just pretend it didn't happen
那就当作没这件事吧
madam
夫人
You didn't tell me honestly at first I'm very disappointed
您一开始没有老实告诉我 就让我很失望了
Mutual trust is the basic condition for doing business, right?
互信是做生意的基本条件吧
I understand
我明白了
If you want more
若您还想要更多
Please give me some time to think about it
请给我一点时间考虑
But madam
不过 夫人
Please don't give me this kind of thing again
请别再给我这种东西了
what is this
这是什么
You are not asking us to remit money in installments into these head accounts?
您不是要求我们分次汇款 到这些人头帐户里吗
What are you doing?
到底在搞什么
Can’t you even grasp the whereabouts of Li Douxue?
连个李斗学的行踪都无法掌握吗
Sorry, he seems to know we're following him Just sneaked away
抱歉 他似乎知道我们在跟踪他 就偷偷溜走了
Don't quibble
不要狡辩
Go out and find someone quickly
快点出去找人
OK
好的
Looks like something isn't going well
看来有事情进行得不太顺利
If you need my help please just ask
如果需要我帮忙 请尽管说
I'm always at your service
我随时都会为你效劳
do you want to help me
你要帮我吗
Maybe he wants to threaten me?
应该是想威胁我吧
You are a person who wants to do great things
你一个要做大事的人
Why are you so vindictive?
怎么这么爱记仇呢
Really? I also want to do big things
是吗 我也想做大事
But there are strong shackles on my feet
但有个坚固的脚镣铐住我的脚
Don't think of me as a shackle
别把我当作是脚镣
We are like the crocodile and the toothpick bird symbiotic relationship
我们就像鳄鱼和牙签鸟的 共生关系
If you think about it this way, you'll feel better.
这样想的话 心里会好受一点吧
Are you definitely symbiotic?
你确定是共生
Isn't it parasitic?
不是寄生吗
Either symbiotic or parasitic
不管是共生或寄生
Anyway, we have to live together.
总之都是要一起活下去的
If it is a parasite Annihilation is good for the body, right?
如果是寄生虫 歼灭才对身体有益吧
if lion and tiger Fighting in an empty field
如果狮子和老虎 在空荡的原野上打架
Do you know who will win?
你知道谁会赢吗
The answer is...no winner
答案是…没有赢家
Lions and tigers know each other well
狮子和老虎对彼此都很了解
Even if you kill the opponent, you will win
就算杀死对方 自己获胜
He will also die from serious injuries
自己也会因为受重伤而死
So lions and tigers avoid each other
所以狮子和老虎会避开彼此
They will never fight
它们绝对不会打架
so
所以呢
What Team Leader Wu means is are you a lion or a tiger
吴组长的意思是 你是狮子或老虎吗
Even if I want to die, I won’t die by myself
要死也不会自己去死
Is that so?
是这样吗
I think you're just a leech
我倒觉得你不过是只水蛭
It will only cause trouble to others and suck their blood.
只会带给别人困扰 吸别人的血
There are hundreds of harms and no benefits
有百害而无一利
But are you really not going to join hands with me?
不过 你真的不打算和我携手吗
Whatever you want to do with my help
只要有我的帮助 你想做的事
the person you want There’s still someone I want to win with
你想得到的人 还有想赢过的对象
I can help you achieve it all
我全都能帮你达成
Didn't you hear what I just said?
你没听到我刚刚说的话吗
Get out of my way right now
马上从我面前滚开
In this case…
既然如此…
I'd rather be respectful than obey your orders.
我就恭敬不如从命了
Aunt, what can you do?
伯母 您有什么事吗
I...I want to discuss something with you
我…有事想找你商量一下
What's going on?
是什么事呢
Douxue and Zhenyu are both back
斗学和贞玉都回来了
There's only one thing left for me to do now
我现在要做的就剩下一件事了
But that thing...
但那件事…
If others knew they might be scared
要是被其他人知道 他们可能会吓到
I really don't know what to do
我真的不知道该怎么做
Aunt, what's going on?
伯母 是什么事呢
Having said that What is Douxue doing now?
话说回来 斗学他现在在忙些什么呢
Actually, I also have something to tell you.
其实我也有事要跟您说
My name is Choi Cheol-woong
我是崔哲雄
it's me
是我
Brother
哥
you are still alive
你还活着啊
What a fuss
真是大惊小怪
Didn’t you already know that?
你不是早就知道了吗
Yes
是啊
But when you come back Why are you contacting me now?
不过你回来后 怎么现在才跟我联络
Is what you said true?
你说的是真的吗
Aunt, I'm really sorry
伯母 真的非常抱歉
I should have told you earlier
我应该要早点告诉您的
Douxue did not commit murder but was blamed for it
斗学没有犯下杀人罪却背上黑锅
It's really pitiful
真的太可怜了
Oh my god
天啊
What should I do?
这该怎么办
Oh my God, what should we do when we fight?
天啊 我们斗学该怎么办
OMG…
天啊…
What should we do when we fight?
我们斗学该怎么办
So...that's when Douxue's dad would...
所以…那时斗学的爸才会…
Things are unpredictable
世事难料啊
And this isn't some theft or robbery.
而且这又不是什么偷拐抢骗的事
Tetsuo should know it by now, right?
哲雄现在也该知道了吧
This incident will make Douxue and Tetsuo The relationship between the two becomes more complicated
这件事会让斗学跟哲雄 两人关系变得更复杂
That uncle really has a wooden head You didn't even tell me
那个大叔真的是木头脑袋 竟然都没跟我说
This can't go on like this
这样下去不行
It's really time for me to show up now
我现在真的该出面了
OMG…
天啊…
"Can I come back to you again?"
"我能再回到你身边吗"
"trembling eyes"
"颤抖的眼神"
"Looks more sad"
"显得更加哀戚"
"My heart is swaying in the desolate sky"
"我的心在荒凉的天空中飘摇"
"your name"
"你的名字"
"It's deeply etched in my heart"
"深深刻在我心上"
What's that look in your eyes?
你那是什么眼神啊
You're happy to see me
是见到我很开心
Are you still disappointed to see me?
还是见到我很失望呢
Nothing, I just find it unbelievable
没什么 我只是觉得很难以置信
Take a seat
坐吧
I thought you would at least pretend Very happy to see me
我还以为你至少会装出 很开心见到我的样子
i'm happy to meet you
我很开心见到你
Dingchen originally wanted to come together
定辰本来说要一起来
I was the one who stopped her
是我阻止她的
This is an issue between the two of us.
这是我们两人之间要解决的问题
if you are still alive You should at least contact me.
你还活着的话 至少也该跟我联络吧
Do you know how much I blame myself and suffer?
你知道我有多么自责和煎熬吗
Those who kill people are in so much pain
杀人的家伙都那么痛苦了
The guy who fell into the cold sea after being shot...
中枪后掉进冰冷大海里的家伙…
How much pain and suffering must it be?
又该有多痛苦和煎熬呢
Was it me who fired the gun?
难道是我开的枪吗
I sincerely hope you can escape overseas smoothly
我是真心希望你能顺利逃到海外
Be a fugitive?
当个逃亡者吗
If you live, you must wander around
如果活着必须漂泊四方
What's the difference between death and death?
跟死了又有什么两样
so
所以呢
Are you here for revenge? Do you want me to apologize?
你是来报仇的吗 要我道歉吗
Tetsuo, the so-called apology
哲雄 所谓的道歉
You don't do it when the person who got beaten wants you to apologize.
不是挨揍的人要你道歉时才做的
The person who did it should have apologized.
动手的人本来就该道歉
Brother, do you know my current position?
哥 你知道我现在的职位吧
If I have to deal with a small character like you
我如果要对付像你这种小角色
It's so easy
简直易如反掌
of course i know
我当然知道
I'm just a little hooligan
我只是区区一个小流氓
It's hard to deal with prosecutors
要对付检察官都很辛苦了
You are a senior official in Nanshan How dare I mess with you
你可是在南山的高官 我怎么敢惹你
I'm not that stupid
我可不是那么愚蠢的人
So what exactly do you want?
那你想要的到底是什么
I want to use my original identity before I die
我想在死前用我原本的身分
Live life quietly
安安静静地过生活
That's enough
这样就够了
Is that it?
就这样吗
wait until the time is right
等到时机成熟时
I will take my family to live abroad
我会带着家人到国外生活
What about Dingchen?
那定辰呢
Of course she wants to go with me
她当然要跟我一起去
She is my fiancée
她可是我的未婚妻
What if I don't agree?
如果我不同意呢
Tetsuo
哲雄
I know how much you like Dingchen
我知道你有多喜欢定辰
But she is not an object
但她不是物品
It's not something you can get if you want it
不是你想得到就能得到的东西
Regardless of the ends of the earth Dingchen will go with me
无论天涯海角 定辰都会跟我一起走
So just let us go
所以你就放我们走吧
I beg you
我拜托你
i will let go
我会放手
Only you can leave
只有你能离开
Tetsuo
哲雄
I can't let Dingchen go
我不能放定辰走
Anyway, it’s impossible for Dingchen to be with you.
反正定辰跟你之间是不可能的
She also knows that I went to jail on your behalf
她也知道我代替你坐牢的事
I'm not trying to hold on to her
我不是要抓着她不放
in a lifetime All have to live a life of escape
在一个一辈子 都要过着逃亡的生活
There's a guy who could go to jail at any time.
随时都有可能入狱的家伙身边
I can't let her do that
我不能放任她那样
It doesn't matter even if the person beside her isn't me
就算在她身边的人不是我也无妨
But I can't just watch her become unhappy
但我无法眼睁睁看她变得不幸
You really... haven't changed at all
你真是…一点也没变
You are the one
你才是
you only think of yourself
你只会想到你自己
This really hasn't changed at all
这一点真是完全没变
If you are willing to let us go
如果你愿意对我们放手
I originally planned to sincerely forgive you.
我本来打算真心原谅你的
The life I lost because of you
我因为你而失去的人生
And…
还有…
My father's death was in vain
我爸爸的枉死
I just want to forget everything
我只是想忘记一切
Live life quietly
安安静静地过生活
Is this such a difficult request?
这是这么困难的请求吗
Just such a dream
只是这样的梦想
people like me
像我这种人
Are you not qualified to have it, you brat?
就没资格拥有吗 你这臭小子
No…
不…
You can live the happy life of your dreams
你可以过你梦想中幸福的生活
I do owe you something
我也确实对你有所亏欠
So…
所以…
I just said I would let you go
我刚刚说我会放过你啊
You will return to Japan within a week
你在一周之内回日本
Living as an overseas Chinese named Lee Hyung-guk
用侨胞李亨国的身分生活
That way you'll be fine
那样你就不会有事
Do you know
知道吗
Tetsuo
哲雄啊
Really not possible?
真的不行吗
Does it have to go to this point?
非得做到这种地步吗
Douxue
斗学
How is it
怎么样
Didn't he apologize to you?
他没跟你道歉吗
Does that kid have any conscience?
那小子到底有没有良心
How could I ruin your life like that? I still haven’t apologized to you…
怎么可以那样毁了你的人生 还不跟你道歉…
I thought about it on the way back
我在回来的路上想了想
Tetsuo may not be wrong
哲雄可能没有错
what
什么
People change depending on where they are But people don't change
人会因为所在的位置而改变 但人不会变
Choi Cheol-woong in high school and Choi Cheol-woong now
高中时的崔哲雄和现在的崔哲雄
Hasn't it changed at all? It's always the same?
不就一点也没变 始终如一吗
In the eyes of Cui Cheol-woong
在崔哲雄眼中
I have always been the son of their working parents.
我一直都是他们家长工的儿子
No wonder some people say
难怪有人说
People only change before they die
人只有在临死之前会改变
Because it is impossible for people to change
因为人是不可能改变的
That bad guy…
那个坏家伙…
He wants me to keep you within a week
他要我在一周内留下你
leave korea
离开韩国
That way nothing will happen to me
那样我才不会有事
you don't have to worry
你不用担心
As long as I'm here, that guy can't hurt you.
有我在 那家伙就伤害不了你
I will help you block all attacks
我会帮你挡下所有攻击
Our opponent is not just Choi Cheol-woong
我们的对手不仅仅是崔哲雄
And Huang Zhongcheng and Jiang Ruzhen
还有黄忠诚和姜汝珍
This is going to be a tough battle
这会是场艰难的仗
Douxue, why are you like this?
斗学 你干嘛这样
I am the publisher of a current affairs magazine
我是时事杂志的发行人
Media people who monitor power
监视权力的媒体人
Dingchen
定辰
Although Tetsuo is bad
哲雄虽然坏
But he has always been sincere to you Don’t you know that too?
但他对你一直都是真心的 你不也知道吗
If the matter is revealed
如果把事情爆料出去
he might lose everything Doesn't that matter?
他可能会失去一切 那样也没关系吗
Break the news
爆料吧
Let’s break the news
还是爆料吧
Choi Cheol-woong is really bad
崔哲雄真的很坏
I feel uncomfortable treating him like that. But…
那样对他我心里也不舒服 但是…
you endured so much pain
你承受了那么多痛苦
I have to continue living in pain That's hell for me
还要继续痛苦地活着 那对我来说才是地狱
So…
所以…
Strike first before he hurts you.
在他伤害你之前 先发制人吧
(Tiandi Entertainment New Era Food)
(天地娱乐 新时代食品)
I have never heard of these companies
我没听过这些公司
Are these accounts associated with your company?
这些是和你们公司有关的帐户吗
That's right
是没错
But how did you get this
但你怎么会拿到这个
I'm using another account why did he give them these accounts
我用的是其他人头帐户 他为什么给他们这些帐户
This is usually done
一般都是这么做的
If you have a large sum of money that you don’t want to be traced
如果有一大笔钱不想被追查
This is how you launder money
就要用这种方式洗钱
The more you share, the less suspicious you will be.
分得越多越不会令人起疑
But…
不过…
Mom, where did you invest a lot of money?
妈 你在哪投资了大钱吗
Did dad tell you about these accounts?
这些帐户是爸告诉你的吗
No, your dad doesn't know
不 你爸爸不知道
I have a problem with President Qin
我跟琴会长出了点问题
Team leader Oh went to see Chairman Geum Man-chul
吴组长去找琴万哲会长
I want him to invest my money Remit the refund to these accounts in batches
要他把我投资的钱 分批汇到这些帐户返还
Originally…
本来…
If you want to launder money, you should report it to your superiors first.
如果要洗钱 应该先向上级报告
But I haven't heard about it, Mom.
但我没听说过这件事 妈
And these accounts
还有这些帐户
Not for private use
不能用于私人用途
What does Team Leader Wu want to do?
吴组长到底想做什么
Forget it
算了
He probably just wants to get his money back safely
他应该只是想安全地把钱拿回来
And you and your father don’t know about this.
而且这件事你和你爸爸不知道
You go in and have a rest.
你快进去休息吧
Right
对了
Mom
妈
What's wrong
怎么了
nothing
没什么
What on earth happened
到底是什么事
I'll tell you later
以后再告诉你吧
Seoul is really different
首尔果然不一样
(Prosecutor Kim Seong-yup)
(检察官 金圣叶)
Hello
您好
You come from the seaside
你从海边过来
The air quality here is pretty bad, right?
这里的空气品质很糟吧
You are here
您来啦
I'm afraid that heroes will be useless I just came here looking for you
我是怕英雄无用武之地 才找你过来的
You've won the prize
您过奖了
People like you are obsessed with eating three bowls of rice
像你这种人才惦惦吃三碗公
See you later
等会见
Let's have dinner together
一起吃晚餐吧
good
好
Please walk slowly
请慢走
Want to treat me to something delicious?
要请我吃好吃的喔
Hello, I am Jin Shengye
喂 我是金圣叶
Congratulations on being transferred to Seoul
恭喜您被调来首尔
homeless man
流浪汉
Was it because of you that I was transferred here?
我是托你的福才被调来的吗
How can a homeless man like me have that kind of ability?
像我这种流浪汉哪有那种本事
In short
总之
Please sharpen the knife first
请您先把刀磨好
when can i see you
我什么时候才能见到你
Do you want me to go to Seoul Station to find you?
要我去首尔站找你吗
I moved
我搬家了
i will find you
我会去找你
good
好
thank you
谢谢
10 billion won in remittance received
收到100亿韩元的汇款了
My son was saved…
我儿子得救了…
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦了
Give me the seal good
印章给我吧 好
There will be good real estate in the future Could you please help introduce me again?
以后有好的房产 再请你帮忙介绍
What's the problem
有什么问题
madam
夫人
Give me the seal
印章给我吧
this building
这栋大楼
You can make money by buying it
是买到赚到
you are so lucky
您太幸运了
come to congratulate you
来 恭喜您
Then…
那…
Right
对了
The balance of 2 billion will be given to you in one month
20亿的余款一个月后再给您
good
好
No problem
没问题
scared me
吓我一跳
(Restaurant rice soup) "Hello world I'm here"
(饭店汤饭) "Hello world 我在这里"
"My voice gets louder"
"我的声音变得更高昂"
"Bye bye fellers I'm leaving first"
"Bye bye fellers 我先走了"
"There's no reason for me to be here right now"
"我现在没有理由在这里"
"Beats goes on turn up the volume"
"Beats goes on 把声音调大"
"Please pay attention here"
"请大家注意这里"
Don't move at all
通通不要动
"Hit the wall I gather strength"
"Hit the wall 我聚集力量"
"Bet everything and punch hard"
"赌上一切重重挥拳"
"Collect them all and throw them away"
"全收集起来 然后远远抛开"
He brought people here just like you said
他真像你说的带人来了
As expected of Prosecutor Choi
不愧是崔检察官
Really don't keep the promise
真不遵守约定
He wants to cut off my source of money
他是想断掉我的金源
But how can I make him happy?
不过怎么能让他如意
You have to abide by the agreement
你要遵守约定
Give me all your shares
把你的股分都给我
I will
我会的
Master, why are you doing this to me?
老爷 您为什么要这样对我
Didn't I give you all the information?
我不是把情报都给您了
Hey, how can I believe what a gangster says?
喂 我怎么能相信流氓的话
Isn't it?
不是吗
"Don't go too far"
"别走得太远"
"Otherwise I might die"
"否则我可能会死"
How is it
怎么样
The song is very nice
歌很好听耶
Really?
真的吗
It's not in vain that you went to live in the countryside
没白费你跑到乡下去住
Very worth it
很值得
Will your new movie use my songs?
那你这次的新电影会用我的歌吗
ok
好吧
Let's find a suitable script for this song together
我们一起找找适合这首歌的剧本
Dingchen
定辰
I have my eye on a good script
我有看中一个不错的剧本
Really?
真的吗
Tetsuo
哲雄
what are you doing
你来做什么
I said we don't have to meet again, right?
我说过我们不必再见面了吧
I came to see you today for official business
我今天来找你是为了公事
I'll go home first
我先回家罗
Is there any official business between us?
我们之间有什么公事吗
Li Douxue
李斗学
He will be wanted soon
马上就要被通缉了
I'll give him some time
我会给他一点时间
Please help me persuade him Tell him to stop being stubborn and leave the country quickly.
你帮我劝劝他 叫他别固执了 快点出国
Why didn't you apologize to Douxue?
你为什么没跟斗学道歉
Apologize…
道歉…
What can be changed
能改变什么
you really are...
你真的是…
Didn’t you also lie to me?
你不也骗了我
Knowing that Brother Douxue is still alive
明知道斗学哥还活着
And met him
还跟他见面
Hello Cui Zhexiong
喂 崔哲雄
you can't do that to me
你不可以那样对我
why not
为什么不可以
Douxue takes the blame for you How many years have you kept it from me?
斗学帮你顶罪的事 你瞒了我多少年
why don't you apologize to me Don't apologize to Douxue either
你为什么不跟我道歉 也不跟斗学道歉
Why don't you let him go?
你为什么不肯放过他
His friend sacrificed himself for you
他这个朋友为你牺牲了自己
You can't do that to him, right?
你才不能那样对他吧
I'm worried that you will become unlucky
我是担心你会变不幸
I don't want to see you become unhappy
我不愿意看你变得不幸
Do you want to run away with Brother Dou for the rest of your life?
你要跟斗学哥一起逃亡一辈子吗
Even if I have to run away for the rest of my life, it doesn't matter
就算要逃一辈子也无所谓
I will protect Douxue
我会保护斗学的
Reporter Shen
申记者
Have you received the information?
你收到资料了吧
Please start preparing
麻烦你开始准备
(Youth Film Company)
(青年电影公司)
something went wrong
出了点问题
It turns out that Lee Doo-hak is working for Chairman Chae Dong-pal
原来李斗学在为蔡东八会长工作
what
什么
Hello
喂
What's wrong?
怎么了吗
Why didn't you say anything, President?
您怎么没说呢 会长
Li Douxue works under you
李斗学在您的手下工作
Li Douxue
李斗学
Who is Li Douxue?
李斗学是谁
Lee Hyung-guk…
李亨国…
Lee Hyung-guk
李亨国啊
Yes, he works for me.
没错 他在我手下工作
But I need to introduce my subordinates Do you know me?
不过我有必要介绍我的手下 给你认识吗
Li Douxue No...
李斗学 不…
Li Hengguo
李亨国
He is a prisoner who committed a crime in Korea and fled abroad.
是在韩国犯罪逃到国外的犯人
Please let him return to Japan immediately
请您立刻让他回日本
Otherwise…
否则…
You want to do business in Korea
您要在韩国做生意
You will encounter a lot of problems, President
会遇到不少问题 会长
I don’t know what crime Li Douxue committed
我不知道李斗学犯下了什么罪
I don't know that person
我不认识那个人
The person I know is named Li Hengguo
我认识的人 叫李亨国
He has not committed any crime
他没犯过任何罪
Is one of my men young man who works hard
是一个在我手下 认真工作的年轻人
I can't do it just because of a word from the prosecutor
我不能只因为检察官的一句话
Let the people I need go back to Japan
就让我需要的人回日本
Chairman, words to protect the prisoner
会长 保护犯人的话
You will also be punished
您也会受罚
are you threatening us
你是在威胁我们吗
not a threat
不是威胁
I'm worried about the president
我是担心会长
Haicheng
海成
Please come back
请回吧
Why didn't the conversation go smoothly?
怎么 谈得不顺利吗
Yes
是啊
people don't know yet What kind of person is Li Douxue?
人们还不知道 李斗学是什么样的人
Brother, I gave you a chance
哥 我给过你机会了
I also gave you a chance
我也给过你机会了
But…
不过…
Do you think you can beat me?
你觉得你能赢我吗
Brother, do you think you can beat me?
哥 你觉得你能赢我吗
Who said I want to compete with you?
谁说要跟你比
I really don't care. It's up to you.
我真的无所谓 你自己看着办
You are so smart, how could you not understand?
你这么聪明 怎么会不明白
Once in high school I stole your first place
高中时有一次 我抢走了你的第一名
you asked me then
你当时问过我
congratulations
恭喜你
No, I guessed a few questions
没有啦 我有几题是用猜的
I'm lucky
我是运气好
You worked so hard for Dingchen Are you preparing for the exam?
你是为了定辰才那么努力 准备考试的吗
That's right, it's for Dingchen
没错 是为了定辰
But…
但是…
Do you know what is harder?
你知道更辛苦的是什么吗
It was a thrilling success in staying in second place.
是惊险地维持在第二名
The really hard thing is losing to you on purpose
真正辛苦的是故意输给你
Later…
以后…
I won't let you again
我不会再让你了
good
好
Then let’s compare
那就来比比看
You are here
你来啦
how are you
您好吗
How are you doing?
你过得好吧
Yeah, of course
嗯 当然
But why did you come to me suddenly?
不过您怎么会突然找我来
Actually…
其实…
I'm a little busy now
我现在有点忙
If it's nothing urgent
如果没什么急事
I'll come back to you later
我之后再来找您
I heard you did that
听说那是你做的
what
什么
I heard that in Lishui that year
听说当年在丽水
You did that
那件事是你做的
Right…
对…
Your days
你这段日子
It must be very painful.
心里一定很煎熬吧
What's wrong
怎么了
Did Brother Douxue say that?
是斗学哥说的吗
You asked him to go to the media to break the news.
你叫他去找媒体爆料
He said he killed someone at that time
说当时杀人的
It's not Lee Doo Hak, it's Choi Cheol Woong
不是李斗学 是崔哲雄
You asked him to go to the media to break the news.
你叫他去找媒体爆料
What's wrong with you, Tetsuo?
你怎么了 哲雄
Yeah, I'm a little weird today
是啊 我今天有点奇怪
Then I'll leave first
那我先走了
Tetsuo…
哲雄…
Tetsuo, listen to me...
哲雄 你听我说…
Tetsuo
哲雄
Tetsuo... listen to me
哲雄… 你听我说
Go in and have a rest.
您快进去休息吧
Listen to me
你听我说嘛
Tetsuo…
哲雄…
Tetsuo
哲雄
Listen to me
你听我说嘛
This is specially made in Japan
这是在日本特制的
You don't want to eavesdrop on how we scold you, do you?
你不是想偷听我们怎么骂你吧
thank you
谢谢
There is no such thing as a free lunch I want to return the favor from now on
世上没有白吃的午餐 以后要还我人情
Just give me the recording
你只要把录音给我
Then just take the money and go abroad.
之后再拿着钱去国外就行了
so i
所以我
Can there be a happy ending?
能有个快乐的结局吗
Although I don't want you to do that
虽然我不想让你那样
But you go
但你走吧
Leave this country
离开这个国家吧
Only in this way can this country become cleaner.
那样这个国家才能变干净点
However
不过
If you can't get the evidence
你如果拿不到证据
Just waiting to be thrown into the Nanji Island garbage dump
就等着被丢去兰芝岛垃圾场
Now that we're on the same boat
既然上了同一条船
Let me tell you something interesting as a gift
我告诉你一件有趣的事当礼物吧
Although I don’t know what you want to do
虽然不知道你又想搞什么鬼
But nothing can scare me anymore There's nothing else I want to know
但已经没什么事能吓得倒我 我也没什么想知道的了
Choi Cheol-woong’s biological father…
崔哲雄的亲生父亲…
You thought it was Minister Huang Zhongcheng?
你以为是黄忠诚部长吧
Actually not
其实不是
President Cai Dongba called me
蔡东八会长打给我
I heard you went to see him
听说你去找过他
Yes
对
You should have discussed this with me before you went.
你去之前应该先跟我商量的
sorry
对不起
I see you are busy with the election
我看您在忙选举的事
Don't want to cause any trouble to you
不想给您添麻烦
That’s why I want to solve it myself
所以才想自己解决
Let's wait first
先等等吧
Chairman Cai Dongba said he is very capable
蔡东八会长说他很能干
If you send him back to Japan Chairman Cai cannot cooperate with us
如果送他回日本 蔡会长就无法和我们合作
The amount of money invested in this election is astronomical
投入在这场选举的钱是天文数字
All bullets must be cherished
必须珍惜所有子弹
We can't do it for a gangster Give up the entire ammunition depot
我们不能为了一个流氓 放弃整个弹药库吧
minister
部长
Li Douxue
李斗学
Not an ordinary gangster
不是普通的流氓
Is it because of Dingchen?
是因为定辰吗
It’s all reached this point I think you are not destined
都到这种地步了 我想你们没有缘分
You'd better forget her
你还是忘记她吧
I sent others to monitor Li Douxue
我派其他人去监视李斗学
No, let me finish it.
不 让我来收尾吧
You give me enough is enough
你给我适可而止
go out
出去吧
National security is about to collapse
国家安保要崩溃啦
Why are you sighing so loudly?
为什么叹这么大口气
Why? What's on your mind?
怎么 你有什么心事吗
How
怎么
Do parasites still want to share my worries?
寄生虫还想分担我的心事吗
Share everything with the host
和宿主分担一切
Is it the fate of parasites?
是寄生虫的命运吧
I say you
我说你
What is it between my mother and President Geum Man-chul? What the hell?
到底在我妈跟琴万哲会长之间 搞什么鬼
Why should we give the company’s account to Qin Wanzhe?
为什么要把公司的帐户给琴万哲
Do you want Madam's funds to be traced?
你希望夫人的资金被查到吗
Then you...
那你…
At least report it to me or the minister first. Brat
至少要先跟我或部长报告吧 臭小子
Report…
报告…
Can this be reported?
这事能报告吗
The minister didn’t know that his wife invested in Qin Manzhe
部长不知道夫人投资了琴万哲
I did it for the sake of peace in your family.
我那么做是为了你们的家庭和平
Your reaction is really unpleasant.
你这反应真让人不开心
I said we should respect each other
我说过我们应该互相尊重吧
you parasite
你这寄生虫
How
怎么
I'm not dead
我没死
Does it make you depressed?
让你很郁闷吗
Yes, brat
对 臭小子
I'm very depressed
我很郁闷
Do you think the minister will be your backer? until when
你以为部长会当你的靠山 到什么时候
Do you think he will be your supporter?
你认为他会当你的靠山吗
I don’t know whose child it is
都不知道是谁的孩子
what
什么
Even a gangster can't be dealt with well
连个流氓也处理不好
Useless trash
没用的废物
Cui Zhexiong knew that I had transferred the company's account Gave it to Qin Wanzhe
崔哲雄知道我把公司的帐户 给了琴万哲
So even if Qin Manzhe transfers money, I can't get the money either
所以就算琴万哲汇钱过去 我也拿不出钱了
what
什么
I won't get half a dime this way.
这样我就拿不到半毛钱了
I have no money and I have no energy to work.
没钱 我也没干劲工作
I'll give it to you
我给你吧
How to give
怎么给
I will first transfer 1 billion won to your account
我会先汇10亿韩元到你的帐户
The rest is waiting for you to get the evidence.
剩下的等你把证据弄到
Pay the money in one hand and deliver the goods in one hand
再一手交钱 一手交货
Then you remit the money immediately
那你马上汇款
I will take action immediately after confirmation
确认后我就立刻行动
(Remittance of 1 billion won by Lee Hyung-guk)
(汇入 10亿韩元 李亨国)
Are you all ready?
大家都准备好了吧
Yeah
嗯
Get Huang Zhongcheng and find someone to kill him After Douxue’s father’s evidence
拿到黄忠诚找人撞死 斗学父亲的证据后
Dingchen will break the news in a current affairs magazine
定辰就会在时事杂志上爆料
Prosecutor Kim Sung Ye will start taking action
金圣叶检察官就会开始行动
Jiang Ruzhen abused her privileges
姜汝珍滥用特权
Huang Zhongcheng abetted murder
黄忠诚教唆杀人
Coupled with the investigation of illegal funds by the Ministry of Security and Enterprise
再加上安企部非法资金的调查
It will continue wave after wave
会一波接一波地延续下去
Then let you help him push it down What about Choi Cheol-woong, who was convicted of murder?
那让你帮他顶下 杀人罪的崔哲雄呢
At the same time as his parents' downfall.
在他父母垮台的同时
He will also hit rock bottom at the same time
他也会同时坠入谷底
Everyone listen up
大家听好了
no second chance Can't make any mistakes
没有第二次机会 不能有任何失误
good
好
Let's go catch the bad guys together
一起去抓坏人吧
Let's go
走吧
Take a seat
坐吧
Thank you very much for taking the time to come here.
辛苦您 特意拨空前来
Okay, tell me what the emergency is.
好 是什么急事你说吧
Just say it quickly
你快说吧
I'm sorry to say this to you
很抱歉跟您说这种话
But I might have to leave you
但我可能要离开您了
what does this mean
这是什么意思
Didn't we promise that we would go to the end together?
我们不是说好会一起走到最后
my ability is insufficient I can only accompany you here
我的能力不足 只能陪您到这里了
The recent troubles have caused you I'm sorry
最近几次闯祸连累到您 我很抱歉
Why are you doing this? It's all in the past.
干嘛这样 都是过去的事了
Everyone has shortcomings
每个人都有缺点
There will be a presidential election in the future The battle for the parliamentary election is about to be fought
以后还有总统大选 议会选举的仗要打
I can rest assured that you are not here Who to leave the matter to?
你不在 我能放心地 把事情交给谁
beside the minister
部长身边
There are many younger than me more capable person
有很多比我更年轻 更有能力的人
Especially Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong
尤其 还有崔哲雄检察官
You are because I kept Tetsuo by my side
你是因为我把哲雄留在身边
Are you disappointed in me by keeping your distance?
和你保持距离 对我很失望吗
No
不是
The minister takes care of me more than anyone else
部长比任何人都照顾我
You will always be my captain
您永远都是我的队长
I was definitely not disappointed
我绝对没有感到失望
But…
不过…
I guess this is all I can do
我想我只能做到这里了
He often gets into arguments with Prosecutor Choi
经常跟崔检察官起争执
I'm tired too
我也累了
Please accept my request
请您接受我的请求
you really
你真是的
Please, Minister.
拜托您了 部长
so sad
真令人伤心
Got it, that's it
知道了 就这样吧
I have something to tell you before I leave
在离开前 我有话要跟您说
Do you remember Lee Yong-deok?
您记得李勇得吗
who
谁
Lee Yongde…
李勇得…
The one who killed Lee Doo-hak's father Lee Jong-ho truck driver
撞死李斗学的爸爸李钟昊的 卡车司机
I heard that after Lee Doo-hak returned to Korea,
听说李斗学回到韩国后
I've been looking for Lee Yongdeok
一直在找李勇得
what
什么
He seemed to suspect that someone was instigating him to kill someone.
他好像在怀疑有人教唆他杀人
If he finds Li Yongde I suspect it was the Minister who ordered you
他如果找到李勇得 怀疑是部长您指使的
Things are going to get tricky
事情会变得很棘手吧
Team Leader Wu
吴组长
Be careful what you say
说话小心点
Sorry
不好意思
You should figure it out on your own before you leave.
你在离开前自己想办法处理吧
Yes I will handle it properly
是 我会妥善处理的
And…
还有…
I have one more thing to tell you
我还有一件事要告诉您
I would say this
我会这么说
Totally out of loyalty to you
完全是出自于对您的忠诚
Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong
崔哲雄检察官
Not your biological son
不是您的亲生儿子
Sorry, Minister
对不起 部长
But I really can't stand it
但我实在看不下去
You've been kept in the dark
您一直被瞒在鼓里
Who else knows about this besides you?
除了你 还有谁知道这件事
I'm just telling you
我只有和您说而已
Tetsuo is not my child
哲雄不是我的孩子
I already knew it
我早就知道了
But why do you…
但您为什么…
I just...
我只是…
I don’t want the person I’ve been waiting for all my life
不希望我等了一辈子的人
Just leave me again
再离开我而已
Choi Cheol-woong is also excellent
崔哲雄也很优秀
Enough to be my child
足以当我的孩子
now i understand
现在我明白
Why is my wife so protective of you?
我太太为什么那么袒护你了
Tetsuo too
哲雄也是
Ruzhen, it must be very hard for you, right?
汝珍因为你一定很辛苦吧
No
不
you misunderstood
您误会了
minister
部长
for our family
为了我们一家人
Please be loyal until the end
请你忠诚到最后
(The final episode will be broadcast tomorrow night)
(明晚将播出完结篇)
(Preview of next episode)
(下集预告)
what spy
什么 间谍
It doesn't seem safe here either
这里好像也不安全
If you resist, you can shoot him
如果反抗可以开枪射杀
shoot to kill
开枪射杀
Please post the news tomorrow
请明天就发布新闻
I'll go to the prosecutor myself
我会自己去找检察官
Tetsuo…
哲雄…
Is it really our child?
真的是我们的孩子吧
This is related to the lives of the minister and Tetsuo
这关乎到部长和哲雄的性命
It's also about your life
也关乎到您的性命
Please save Tetsuo
求求你救救哲雄
Surrender
自首
It's not enough to help you with one murder.
帮你扛一次杀人罪还不够
Now you want me to help you carry it Are you guilty of killing my father?
现在还要我帮你扛下 你杀了我爸爸的罪吗
You can't attack each other like this
你们不可以这样互相攻击
You are brothers
你们是兄弟啊
aunt
阿姨
If you don't shoot now, you won't be my son.
你现在不开枪就不是我的儿子
No
不可以
No, Tetsuo
不可以 哲雄
please don't do that
拜托你别那么做